As engineers, there's just one idea you
and I need to win in the age of agents.
Scale your compute to scale your impact.
The goal is clear, but the path is less
clear. The big open question the best
engineers are asking is how exactly
should you orchestrate your agents for
maximum impact? And there's no shortage
of options. Boris and Peter are saying
loop engineering is the future and
prompt engineering is already dead. I
completely disagree with this. There's
the Ralph style to-do list to keep your
agents focus on a massive list of work.
Fable is going to love Ralph. Then
there's classical sub aent delegation
and many many more patterns. I've been
engineering for over 15 years and
building with agents since it was first
possible. And we have to call out the
fact that these AI labs have massive
incentives to keep you and I spending
tokens, token maxing, when the truth is
there's a dozen different agentic
patterns you can use to ship with
agents. One of my favorite patterns is
three tier agent orchestration.
Orchestrators prompt the leads. Leads
prompt the specialized agent experts.
But every multi- aent approach has
similar problems. The big three being
how do you start, interact, and improve
your growing fleet of agents. If you're
vibe coding or token maxing, this
doesn't matter at all. You can spin up
20 agents in a loop and look the other
way. On this channel, we don't vibe
code. We agentic engineer because an
agent you can't monitor is an agent you
can't improve. I have three multi- aent
orchestration problems I'm going to
solve and I'm looking at CMUX as a
potential solution to this problem. As
we work through the feature set of CMUX,
I want to share with you how I'm
continuing to learn new tools and
technology with agents. If these ideas
interest you, smash the like button,
lock in, and let's improve our agent
orchestration.
Whenever I sit down to learn a new tool
or technology, I have a state-of-the-art
agent build out a comprehensive HTML
file that I can use to visually
understand, study, and master new tools.
So, that's how we're going to learn CMOX
right now. Let's start with the problem.
What problems are we going to solve? I
don't start with tools. Problems come
first, tools come second. I know I'm
late to the Semox game, but I don't
really care outside of experimentation.
If I don't need a tool, I don't pick it
up until I have a problem. First, I have
three problems surrounding multi-agent
orchestration that you likely have, too.
Let's see if can solve three popular
multi- aent orchestration problems. So,
first off, no programmatic access to
your agents. This is a massive problem
because it means you're the bottleneck
and it keeps you in the loop all the
time, meaning your agents can never move
at the agentic speed. The big question
is, can Semuk solve this? The answer is
of course yes. The core value
proposition of tools like CMUX and the
triedand-true T-M is this exactly. They
give you agentic access to every single
terminal. An agent you can't see is an
agent you can't improve. This is going
to be increasingly controversial. A lot
of engineers are turning off their
brain. They're not studying what their
agents are doing. They're spinning up
fleets and they're ignoring the journey,
all the mistakes, all the successes, all
the things that they would want to
emphasize, reproduce, and cut out of
their workflow is completely ignored.
This is one of the key differences
between vibe coding and agentic
engineering. An agent you can't see is
an agent you can't improve. I need to be
able to see everyone of my agents. Okay?
It doesn't matter if it's cloud code,
pi, open code, codeex. I need to be able
to see it, monitor it and understand
when things are going right so I can
re-emphasize that behavior in the agent
via the core 4 or I need to know when
things are going wrong so I can present
negative rewards. Okay, so can Semox
solve that problem for us? Yes, it can.
We have per workspace color roll icons,
identity, we have tabs, we have banners.
We have everything we need to quickly
jump into an agent and see it. Quick
teaser here. I have semox ready to go
and you can see here we have a great
breakdown the kind of fundamental pieces
of a tool where we can quickly see
observe and therefore improve everything
right we have a cloud code agent we have
a codeex agent we have two pi agents
running the minimax m3 and the jm 5.2
too. We'll get back to this in a second.
Let's fully understand every single
problem. And this is a big one. It's
increasingly becoming a problem as I
deploy more and more agents and set up
new teams to do specific sets of work
extraordinarily well. If you're building
custom agents, you're running into this
problem, too. If you're deploying 5, 10,
20 plus agents, you have also seen this
problem. Booting an agent team by hand
kills the agentic speed. It just takes
too much time. So, can T-book solve
this? Of course, yes, it can. and it has
reusable session files. But more
importantly, this tool has agentic
access. If a tool has agentic access,
that means you can move at the agentic
speed and solve problems in natural
language with well- constructed prompts.
Okay, so these are the problems we're
going to solve. CMOX has solutions to
all of them. I think the question is, do
you have to use CMX or is something like
T-Max going to get you all the way there
as well? So, let's dial back into CMOX
and understand what this tool can do and
see if it can help us solve these three
key problems. Agentic access, monitor to
improve, and quick agentic launch for
your thousandth agent run. Not your
first, not your 10th, not your hundth.
So, what is our agent teaching us about
CMX? Let's understand the mental model
that really builds the foundation of
understanding CMOX and other terminal
multiplexes as well. You have the window
which is going to be this entire window
here with control shift N. We can boot
up a brand new window. And then we have
our workspace. Workspaces, you know, we
can boot up with command N. And this is
going to give us a new workspace to set
up teams of agents to set up groups of
terminals to do whatever you need to do.
Then we have PES. The pane is going to
be the actual window. We have a pane
here. We have a pane here. We have one
here, here, and here. It's important to
mention if we do commandt, this opens a
new surface inside of this existing
pane. So we have individual windows. You
can separate and group your agent teams,
your terminals, you can have production,
you can have staging, you can have dev,
we can have workspaces. So for me, I'm
going to put my agent teams on the
workspace level. And then inside of the
workspace, you have your individual
panes. So we have a pane here in my
multi- aent orchestration workflow. I'm
going to put my lead here. And then the
workers go over on the right. So I can
look at the level that I need to to get
the job done while not losing the depth
of visibility into the low-level worker
agents. This is super key, right?
Prompting in a black box in sub agents
is a great place to start. Terrible
place to finish, right? We can do a lot
better than that with the right agentic
tools. That's why we're trying to see if
we can really improve our multi- aent
orchestration abilities. Okay, so that's
the mental model of cmox. And so how do
we control it?
Uh it's pretty simple. Thanks to the
programmatic access, we do four things.
We can send information like send key.
We can then read the screen after the
action has been completed. And then we
can open and close surfaces and the loop
repeats. Okay, so this is how you
control it. We're going to walk through
concrete examples of how you can use
semucks in just a moment here, but
here's an example of the API, right?
Send, read, close surface. You specify
the surface and the exact text you want
to send in. Another powerful part about
CMX, we can build an orchestration agent
around pushing and pulling specific
events from the CMX life cycle and
therefore our agents life cycle. Okay,
so there's a lot of customizability
here. When I sit down to learn a tool, I
use agents the entire time. Learning is
the killer use case for agents. Coding
comes next. in these HTML rich guides. I
want an incremental tier-based
explanation of how I can best use these
tools to solve my specific use case. And
that's exactly what my agent has done
here. A lot of really smart engineers
are turning their brains off. I want to
push back against that. We want to rise
with the ceiling of agentic engineering,
not the floor of vibe coding. Okay. So,
um let's run this, right? Let's
understand CMOX at a deeper level. You
see here, this tool can get very, very
complex. It can help you orchestrate and
do a lot of work. They even have like a
mobile app here. You can access
browsers. There's a lot of cool stuff
you can do with this tool. We're not
going to cover all that. We're going to
focus on the problems we need to have
solved. Whenever I'm learning a new
tool, I like to start super simple,
understand the foundations of the tool,
and then move to more and more complex
scenarios. All right, so let's go ahead
and start from scratch here. I'm going
to open up a terminal, boot up a cloud
code opus window here. If you're working
in the future, you have access to Fable.
I am jealous of you right now. Can't
wait for that model to be turned back
online. Although, it looks like there's
going to be massive delays with getting
that back online. So I have a semox
skill that was built that just makes the
agent aware of the tool. Open a
workspace in a fresh temp directory.
Create 63A files lsla read the output
back and then continue from there. All
right. So we're just having our
orchestrator agent operate on cmox
windows. So let's see how this looks and
I'll hold them both open here at the
same time. So you can see here our
existing agent team window is open. My
agent is operating this window. Okay. So
we have a new workspace here. Inside the
window, we have a pane with a single
tab. You can see there's that ls. You
know, I'm not typing anything here. This
my agent operating a workspace to be
clear. This is bigger than a terminal.
It's done. Right? So, we had an ls all
these mock files it created. Right? If
we close this, do ls ourselves, we can
see them exactly. The great part about
tools like cmox and t-mox is that you
can jump in whenever you need to. Right?
The agent stopping black boxes when you
can actually touch and jump in to the
terminal window. Aentic access here is
super super important. very simple,
great place to start when you're
learning a new tool. Just show a basic
use case of the app. So, let's split
into a grid. I want to see a grid here.
So, I'm going to close our throwaway 60
and we'll work our way up to, you know,
a full multi- aent orchestration example
here. We're just setting the groundwork.
Always start with the fundamentals.
So, this is going to open a 2x two grid
in a new workspace.
There we go. And in each workspace, it's
going to run specific commands. On the
right here, it's just an empty terminal.
Here we have the date being updated per
second. And then we have a tick in the
bottom left. And then in the top left,
we have h top running. Each one of these
clearly documented in the workspace
name. You can see how this can be very
very powerful for agents. Right? So, not
only is this tool helping us move at the
agentic speed, it's giving us access to
quick start commands to run repeat
workflows. All right? So, boot up your
front end, boot up your back end, boot
up all your services, boot up your
database. Let's keep pushing to see how
this tool is differentiated from a tool
like T-Mox because T-Mox is the OG of
this. Let's go and tidy up. Let's have
our agent clean everything up. Take the
dash workspace, rename it, flash it, and
then start closing it. Okay, so this is
where we start pushing into the value
prop of CMX. It can control the PES and
the windows in a very, very precise way.
There's the flash. It updated the name
to retired. So we have live updates
happening at any point in time that we
can agentically program. We can prompt
engineer into the system to really
control the experience of agentic
engineering. And that's really where
this all goes, right? The ultimate user
interface for agentic engineering, the
DX for agentic engineering, it is not
set in stone yet. As much as everyone's
talking about loop engineering and
building these new DXs, there are no
winners yet. Okay? only experimenters,
only researchers, only those pushing
what they can do with agents. So, keep
looking for the optimal developer
experience for your work, for your
agent, so on and so forth. Right? And
that's what we're doing here. We're just
understanding the state space of the
available agentic tools. Okay? And as
you'll notice here, building blocks,
extensibility, adaptability,
pluggability is a key part of great
agentic technology, right? which is why
I'm drawn to CMOX in the first place.
Great. Agentic access renamed Flash.
Close the whole workspace. Great, you
get the picture. Let's get more complex
here. Let's boot up Cloud Code and the
PI coding agent side by side. We're
going to do this in a brand new
workspace. That's the mode I like to
work in here with CMU. So far, I'm
getting into this nice pattern of
creating new workspaces, not Windows.
Two columns here side by side. And one
is PI and one is Claude. And so, another
great piece about this, you can
orchestrate any agent coding tool you
want to. If you're a cloud code guy,
scale up your cloud codes. If you're a
Codeex fan, scale those up. If you're an
open code scrub, go for that. Just
kidding. Just kidding. If you're a PI
coding agent, elite agentic engineer
plugging and playing with your own
custom agent harnesses, then you'll go
for that, right? Opus 4.8, one of the
best orchestrator models in the game
until Fable supersedes it. You can see
here we are orchestrating multiple
coding agents with the orchestrator
agent. Okay, very, very powerful stuff.
I'm using IPI for my PI coding agent.
This is my customized PI coding agent
with several different extensions built
into it. This a specialized developer
experience as an agent harness. So we've
just asked a simple question here about
processes versus threads and they both
answered, right? So nothing special
there, but the value proposition is
obvious. You can boot up agents and you
can prompt agents using cmox and we can
continue to scale this. Okay, so let's
do exactly that. Let's start
orchestrating fleets of agents. Okay, so
let's do a 2x2 fleet. And a really
important piece here that you'll also
notice is that these agents have
completed. They then send a notification
to this top window. Okay? So, say you're
working over here getting things done on
another branch of work, another set of
work. CMU is going to notify you when
this set of agents or single agent if
you want to do one workspace per agent.
It'll let you know when that work is
done. Okay. But here we go. We have a
new fleet. This is our security fleet.
Send up four coding agents. Cloud Code,
Codeex, Pi with Minamax and GLM. Create
a fleet. List the top three security
vulnerabilities you can find in this
repository. So this is a simple mock
repository. This is a waste for these
agents. Not really going to do anything.
But you can see here this is a simple
important idea of literally scaling your
computer to scale your impact. Say you
were looking for security
vulnerabilities in your codebase. You
can spin up one agent and have sub
agents under it run. Or you could set up
different agentic coding tools with
their own unique advantages running
different agents to run the exact same
validation pattern, the exact same
security checks across your codebase.
Okay, this is the simplest clearest
example of scaling your compute to scale
your impact. The big difference here
with a tool like CMX or T-Mox is that
this is fully visible. Okay, so we have
Minamax M3 giving a shot at this GLM 5.2
and of course the state-of-the-art
models GPT 5.5 and Opus 4.8. They're all
applying their opinions, their
perspective, their expertise, their
specific model advantage against this
problem of checking for security
vulnerabilities, a big topic right now
in the age of agents. One of the key
pieces of this is now inside of our
orchestrator because remember the way
I'm looking at this tool is any point to
be able to use my orchestrator to drive
results in any one of my windows, any
one of my workspaces and then the
individual panes, but also have the
ability to go into any individual agents
and really just prompt out and dial into
any details we need to on an agent
level. Okay, so this is important. We
want to be able to jump into the process
at any point, understand what every
agent is doing, who's got the advantage,
who's running patterns we want to
replicate, and who's doing stupid
we don't want to do again. Okay? And
that's on a agent coding tool level, all
the way down to, of course, the model
level. And then further on down, right?
Context, model, prompt, tool, system
prompt, context. So great, these are all
done. And the orchestrator is reading it
back out. This is now in idle mode
because the orchestrator has read the
response. It's read the surface, right?
It knows that things are done. This is
where we start getting out of what T-Max
can do, right? We're working on multiple
problems. We're scaling our computer
scale impact and we can see everything
and we can understand everything. Okay,
fantastic. So, we are doing multi- aent
delegation, but of course, one of the
key things here is any agent can prompt
any other agent. So, I'll just try to do
something random here. Inside of this
cloud code worker, I'll type cmox to
activate the skill. Ping your other
fleet co-workers. So very powerful stuff
here. It's going to read the screen of
each surface. I've been seeing really
really great success with this three
tier architecture with my agents, right?
You have a top level orchestrator. You
then have team leads and then the leads
have workers that actually do the work.
Okay, so we're replicating traditional
hierarchy structures without the true
cons and true problems with hierarchies,
right? This is not a top- down
structure. Any agent can prompt any
agent. You can see that here thanks to
this skill here. We're going to do a
nice simple prompt coming into every
single agent from inside CMX, right? So,
our agents can prompt our agents. This
is a flat hierarchy even though there is
one orchard is at the top. And so, I
like to put my team lead on the left as
you'll see in a moment, but we can just
drag and drop this down here or we'll
move it over here. And this very quickly
kind of shows you the organizational
structure that you can build. Lead here,
workers here. And you can build any
structure you want. The point is is that
the communication channel is flat. All
right. So, fantastic. What else can we
do with this tool? Let's scale into
workspaces. Let's really push what we
can do with this. So, I'm going to copy
this larger prompt here. Going to have
my agent do this here. We're going to
showcase like the importance of
organization inside the workspace. You
can see here we're starting to already
have a lot more organization than normal
if we were just in a single terminal or
if we were using a single terminal with
tabs. We're getting notification events
which are pretty pluggable. You can do a
lot more with them than we are. You can
see here, imagine you're booting up
multiple teams to solve multiple
problems. We have gamma, beta, alpha. We
can jump into these and we can see our
let me pull up the orchestrator so we
can see what's going on here. Our
orchestrator getting work done booting
up sets of agents programmatically.
Let's close our security fleet here.
Okay, so we have gamma, we have beta,
and we have alpha booted up. Okay, so
you know, imagine any multi- aent
orchestration set of teams you want.
That's a key value proposition here. You
have multi- aent coordination at a
massive scale, right? Just an absolutely
massive scale and you're in control and
you have visibility into it. Okay, super
super important. If you hold command,
you can see all the hot keys for each
workspace. This is clearly the unit that
CMX sees as the most important to be
navigating. It's at that workspace
level. But of course, we can quickly
move through all of our surfaces as
well, right? So again, just expressing
the idea here. You can scale agents
across multiple workspaces as well.
So let's look at the scenario where you
need to fix a bug right away. Say
production's going down. Your customers
and your users are completely blocked.
So you're losing money by the second.
Okay. So I'm going to hit new here just
to reboot everything and then paste this
in here. There's a longer prompt, but
we're going to have agents race toward a
solution. Okay. So I'm going to close
all these windows here. Say there's a
production issue and you need to resolve
it yesterday. This is going to be a
differentiating agentic engineering
pattern that you can use. It's super
simple. Throw more compute at the
problem. Have your agents race toward a
solution. We're going to do a needle in
a haystack search. In reality, this will
be a hot fix. You'll need to deploy, but
you can just throw a bunch of agents at
a problem at the same time in parallel.
You want the first available answers so
you can deploy the fix back into
production. Okay. So, in this scenario,
we're going to boot up an eight agent
race to just race toward a solution. So,
there we go. All the windows popping
open here. And we're going to deploy a
variety of compute to get the job done.
This is needle in a hay stack. Capture
the flag. first agent to the goalpost
wins type of task. Okay. And multi- aent
orchestration lets you do this really
really well. Every context model prompt,
every agent coding tool is going to have
their unique advantages, strengths and
weaknesses. And so when you need to
deploy something quickly, when you have
a hot fix you need to deploy, throwing
different types of intelligence at the
problem is going to get you the better
result pretty much every single time if
you're willing to of course pay for the
compute. And so you can imagine, you
know, you have your red team agent race
here and then you might have another set
of agents in a, you know, your
infrastructure agents or your deploy
agents here. And then you might have
your review set of agents here to at
scale quickly review the issue so that
you can then hand it off to your infra
team of agents, right? Your deploy
agents. And now we have a bunch of
compute thrown at the problem. We've got
Opus, we've got Sonnet. And another
advantage here, you can see a couple of
my PI agents didn't even fire. It looks
like an environment variable setup
problem. That's fine. My local agent, my
local Quinn is working. All the codecs
and all the Sonnet models quickly found
the solution. That's done. And now this
issue can be reported. And now we're
waiting for that notification event for
my orchestrator and needs input. There
we go. Okay, so it finally triggered
there. And now our orchestrator should
pick this up. Let's go and see if it
does pick it up cuz all the agents are
complete. Maybe this is a good time for
us to transition a little bit and talk
about the pros and cons of this tool,
right? And maybe my agents just don't
don't understand the tool properly.
That's fine. It could be a mistake on my
part. When you're using tools like this,
these new tools, tools that are just
kind of appearing overnight, and I know
CMX deserves more credit than that. This
is a solid tool that's been around for a
while. There's a whole wave of agentic
tools coming. And you're always going to
want to compare that against tried and
true technology. So, when I sit down to
solve problems and learn with agents,
I'm always comparing against what else
exists. For a lot of the capability
we've looked at here, T-Max can do the
job. The thing is that it's not going to
be as customizable and aesthetic, and
the developer experience, I think, with
T-Max is a little harder to get right.
That's what CMOX does really, really
well. It's made for the modern era of
building with agents programmatically on
Mac devices. Okay, so yeah, probably
should have mentioned that earlier. If
you're on Linux, Windows, WSL, you know,
you're going to need to use a tool like
T-Mox. This is Mac only. The big problem
with this is just maturity, right? These
brand new tools have issues and it could
be me. But you can see here, you know,
in our red team response here, our
orchestrator has done nothing. Check and
understand why you stalled there, right?
Because really we wanted to ping on the
first completion of our tool, right? Our
first completion of any window. Okay, so
foreground 10 minute. Okay, very weird.
So we did get a notification event. uh
it just seems like our agent didn't
register it. This is one of the things I
need to spend more time on to make sure
I'm getting right and it's just one of
the things that you'll have to
understand when you're building and
teaching your agents how to use the
tool. Something can be improved there,
but the high level is still there. There
are notification events you can plug
your agents into to wait for responses
from your agents.
We're going to stand up eight agents
across four workspaces, two agents in
each. Give them each a two column
layout. The left is the agent and the
right is going to be a browser. Now,
this direction is fine. CMX is, you
know, trying to grow as a product, so it
has inapp browsers. That's really cool.
The real killer feature here is
programmability. This is the most
important thing. It's nice that it's
lightweight. Of course, open source is
super important, but customizability is
what comes next. And there's a whole
slew of customization you can build out
into your CMX application that we're
going to gloss over because these are
extra features. You can change the theme
and feel. You can add custom action
buttons. That's all well and good. The
most important thing here by far is a
gentic access, right? This is a huge
theme. This is one of the key pillars of
agentic engineering, right? is making
sure that you have a gentic access to
every tool to every service to every
product that you want to interact with
at the speed of agents not the speed of
humans. I think we can just say that
right in the digital world eventually
the physical world too we move very
slowly now and there are advantages to
moving slowly coding is not our domain
anymore that is the domain of agents
okay but orchestrating intelligence is
our domain this is one of the five
pillars of agentic engineering we've
covered this in a previous video I'll
link that below if you're interested
here's the kind of high level of the
five pillars I'm really really focusing
on right now over 2026 and aentic access
is number five Even your agents should
have agentic access, right? You want
that meta level of control. And this is
all to raise the ceiling of your agentic
engineering, not the floor of vibe
coding. When these mythos class models
come out, a lot of engineers are just
going to sit. They're going to get lazy.
They're going to stop thinking and just
hand the wheel to the agent. On this
channel, we're not going to be doing
that. If you agree with that ideology,
like, follow, subscribe, all that good
stuff. The kind of oneliner is if a tool
does not have programmatic access, I
just completely ignore it. Now I don't
give it another second of my time. Okay.
Agentic access gives you the agentic
speed. Let's see where our team is. FS
delta gamma beta alpha team. Imagine
these are you know the names of features
the names of bug fixes the names of
things you are actually building
against. We have a nice browser on the
side. And we have a two agent team per
workspace to work on that browser. Okay.
So you get the idea here, right? We have
a little custom theming here to help us
get back in the loop when we need to be
in the loop to orchestrate our agents.
So again, you know, having visual
identifiers improves your developer
experience, lets you focus on what
matters the most and then you can just
move on. The biggest risk with CMX is
that this is a new relatively fastmoving
tool. I'm going to be using both of
these tools side by side, not so much
using warp anymore, but CMX and T-Mox
I'm going to be spending some time on.
And that leads us to the kind of final
problem. I need to be able to quickly
launch agents for the thousandth time.
So, let me show you really concretely
how I'm using a tool like this. So,
I have a just file inside of my code
bases and this lets me give a really
quick onetap command to boot up new
agent teams. Okay, so I'll just type
jfast cc. If I hit enter here, I need to
pass in a feature. So, what's the focus
of this agent team? Okay, so I'll type
fast CC and then we'll call this SSC.
Let's assume we're adding server sent
events into our web server. Okay, so
we'll hit enter there and this is going
to pretty much instantly boot up an
agent team and this is a unique agent
team in the multi- aent orchestration
pattern that I like. This is three tier
multi- aent orchestration and it looks
like this. The orchestrator here, team
leads here. Every one of these is a team
lead in my workspace. And so this
specifically is the team lead. Right now
I'm using a GLM 5.2 two and then every
team lead gets access to worker agents.
Okay, so here's my plan agent, here's my
theoretical build agent, here's the
build front end, and here's the testing
agent. Might seem complex to add one
additional level of agent, but it helps
a lot. And I've needed a tool like CMX.
T-Max wasn't cutting it for the right
organizational structure. And so I'm
picking up a tool like CMUX to kind of
help me solve this multi- aent
orchestration problem. these sets of
problems. It's starting agents. It's
monitoring agents so you can improve
them. And then it's being able to scale
your orchestration to whatever level you
need to. And so, as mentioned, this is
not top-down agent communication, right?
Any agent can prompt any agent. I also
have my specialized comsnet PI agent
coding extension, but CMOX lets me push
outside of the extension and have any
agent decoding tool talk to any agent
decoding tool. Thanks to the semox
skill, birectional flat agent
communication is super important while
maintaining an orchestrator, a lead, and
then a worker level setup. And I'll link
the video where we go into multi-tiered
agent orchestration. This isn't for
everyone. A lot of engineers are going
to look at this and say, "Why do I need
this? It's slop. This isn't useful."
That's fine. It just means it's not for
you. Okay? As I mentioned in the
beginning, there's many ways to do this.
You can use the Ralph to-do list. You
can use the new loop engineering
patterns. And you can just use classic
cloud code subbasation delegation that's
fine right they have the slashworkspaces
they have slashloop they have slashgoal
right use whatever works for you my goal
here is just to show you the optionality
of what's available to you and to
reemphasize a gentic access and full
control over the primitives of agentic
engineering right context model prompt
tool once you have an agent up and
running you can scale it right now I
have a team here that has let's say
these are each 1 million contacts each
specialized, that gives me 5 million
tokens of context to work with, quite
literally, right? That's not an
exaggeration. When you put together your
agents in a way where they can all
communicate, you're getting a bigger
team of intelligence to work on your
behalf. Okay, so um you know, what's the
verdict? I like CMX. I'm going to be
using this tool. It stands up to T-Mox
pretty well. I'm going to be keeping my
eye on any glitches or bugs with this
tool, but so far, I'm a big fan. It's
the scriptable service API, the agentic
access that really matters with this
tool. There are a bunch of other
features here I didn't mention. I'm sure
some CMOX hardcore users are going to be
flaming me for this being so relatively
simple. But the key here is it's
programmable, right? That's the most
important thing by far. Aentic access is
a requirement for agentic engineering.
And this is going to compound. Every
single thing you set up here from this
five item list is going to give you a
compounding advantage for agentic
engineering. Once again, we want to be
moving up with the ceiling of agentic
engineering, not the floor of vibe
coding. All these ideas are big ideas we
talk about and really break down in
tactical agentic coding. I'll leave a
link in the description for that if
you're interested in paying a little bit
to get a massive advantage. If you're
not though, that's totally fine. I'm
going leave my entire guide code base
here to really break down Semox
capabilities. If you made it to the end
and you want to see more agentic
engineering content like this, drop a
like, share the video with a friend,
with a co-orker, and then comment down
below. How are you thinking about multi-
aent orchestration? Do you have any
unique experiments or tools you're
running to better scale your computer to
scale your impact? You know where to
find me every single Monday. Stay
focused and keep building.